<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Legals on CoNime</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/legal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Legals on CoNime</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/legal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about-us/</guid>
      <description>About CoNime&#xA;CoNime is an online news portal delivering the latest updates from the world of anime, comics, movies, and games, especially for Indonesian readers. We are committed to providing up-to-date news, episode reviews, anime and comic recommendations, movie and game reviews, as well as thought-provoking opinions for fans.&#xA;We are not an official website of any publisher, anime studio, or game developer. All content is for informational purposes only and aims to enrich the pop culture community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disclaimer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>CoNime Disclaimer&#xA;CoNime is an informational portal covering anime and comics. We are not affiliated with any official content owners or trademarks mentioned. All images, videos, and excerpts are copyrights of their respective owners.&#xA;Any leaks, predictions, or fan-made content are for entertainment purposes only and are not official references. We strive for accuracy but cannot guarantee all information is completely correct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>CoNime Privacy Policy&#xA;Your privacy is important to us. CoNime does not collect any personal data without your permission. If you contact us via a form, your information is only used for communication purposes.&#xA;This website displays third-party advertisements, including Google AdSense, which may use cookies to serve relevant ads. You can disable cookies in your browser settings.&#xA;By using this site, you agree to this privacy policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Service</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/terms-of-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/terms-of-service/</guid>
      <description>CoNime Terms of Service&#xA;By accessing CoNime , you agree to use the content responsibly and not for any illegal or harmful purposes.&#xA;Copying or redistributing content from this site without permission is prohibited. We reserve the right to modify or terminate any part of the service without prior notice.&#xA;If you do not agree with these terms, please do not use our website.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
