<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fighting Game on CoNime</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/tags/fighting-game/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fighting Game on CoNime</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:00:00 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/tags/fighting-game/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bleach: Rebirth of Souls Adds Ranked Mode and Ichigo Kurosaki (Thousand-Year Blood War) DLC</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/games/bleach-rebirth-of-souls-ranked-mode-dlc-ichigo-20250609-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 08:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/games/bleach-rebirth-of-souls-ranked-mode-dlc-ichigo-20250609-en/</guid>
      <description>Bandai Namco has officially announced a major update for Bleach: Rebirth of Souls, including Ranked Matchmaking Mode and the Ichigo Kurosaki (Thousand-Year Blood War Arc) DLC. Season Pass holders can access it from June 10, while the general release is scheduled for June 17, 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon Ball Xenoverse 2 Adds Dragon Ball DAIMA Pack with SS4 Goku &amp; SS3 Vegeta</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/games/dragon-ball-xenoverse-2-daima-pack-20250522-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/games/dragon-ball-xenoverse-2-daima-pack-20250522-en/</guid>
      <description>The Dragon Ball DAIMA Pack is now available for Dragon Ball Xenoverse 2, adding Super Saiyan 4 Goku (DAIMA) and Super Saiyan 3 Vegeta (DAIMA), plus new costumes, accessories, parallel quests, Super Souls, and loading screens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon Ball: Sparking! ZERO Adds Dragon Ball DAIMA Pack 1 DLC Featuring 8 New Characters</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/games/dragon-ball-sparking-zero-daima-dlc-pack1-20250424/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 19:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/games/dragon-ball-sparking-zero-daima-dlc-pack1-20250424/</guid>
      <description>Bandai Namco releases the Dragon Ball DAIMA Pack 1 DLC for Dragon Ball: Sparking! ZERO, adding eight new characters—including Goku (Mini) and Vegeta (Mini) up to Super Saiyan 3—as well as new technique-changing outfits for Goku (Mini). Available for Season Pass holders and as a separate purchase on PlayStation 5, Xbox Series X|S, and PC.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
